Okay, so we thought we'd do this call this month, because I was just asking for
what
calls people might like to see, by the way, please let us know if you've got
any ideas
or anything that you want to learn about with regards to coming, please let us
know, because
we're always looking for new ideas for things to do, you know, after like four
or five years
of doing training calls, it's quite hard to find inspiration. But this one is
really important,
I think, just for us all to get some inspiration and think about what it is
that makes our
calls last longer. Of course, you know, we all want to earn as much money as we
can and
make the most of every client, don't we? So let's have a look at some ways that
we can
make our calls last longer. So connection, obviously, is key here. So the key
to engaging
clients for as long as possible is connection. So obviously, there's different
ways of coming,
but, you know, we talk about this all the time. And, you know, there are some
people that favour
like, you know, it's like any product, you know, there are some people that
favour loads and loads
of sales of a cheaper product. Or there are some people that favour just a few
sales of a product
that costs much more. So that's kind of what this call is about. It's about the
people who's
coming styles are more about making the most of and maybe having a few regulars
that you earn
more from, as opposed to having a large stream of people coming in and out all
the time,
and you're earning little bits off them, which is totally valid. There are two
different ways
of coming. And maybe you do both. But this one, this call is more about the
calls that can last
longer for you and how to keep clients engaged for as long as possible. So it's
focused on connection.
So connection, of course, is what turns a short visit into a long memorable
call. And hopefully,
into a regular as well, because we all know that's what we're kind of aiming
for.
So most clients aren't just seeking visual stimulation. So they're not here
just to look at
what's going on. They're seeking attention, affirmation, and engagement. So
when a client feels
stimulated in the mind and not just in their body, they're more likely to relax
, stay longer,
and return. So it's about building a relationship with them and how they feel
when they're with you.
So the first thing before we even get into thinking about, you know, actual
calls itself
is obviously your profile. So your profile is the first opportunity you have to
connect with
clients. And also to just make clients curious about who you are to help, you
know, build up
the story of who you are, like, whether it's your genuine self or your persona
matter.
It's a place where you can through your pictures and all the things that you
might add on your
profile, you can start to build up a picture for them about who you are.
Obviously, some people
are just clicking through and just seeing maybe the tagline and just your
picture. So not everyone's
going to read your profile. But those that do are important, because they're
the people that
have taken the time to actually read through. And they tend to be really good
regulars,
because they actually want to get to know you a bit more. They want to find out
who they're
going to be talking to. And these are the ones that you can really capitalize
on.
So using your mentor, we do have a document that we can send you all about, you
know,
tips for making your profile look as best as it possibly can. So obviously, you
're thinking
about the photos you've got on there, whether or not they go with your image
that you're trying
to portray. You can have different tabs with different things that you like to
do or different
things about you or the type of clients that you like. So there's loads of
ideas that we can give
you about making your profile as engaging as it can be. And what always opens
up, have a little
look as well, and you know, give you some tips individually, either messaging
your mentor or one
of us, we're always willing to have a little look. It's also good to just have
a flick through and look
at everybody else's profiles, especially the people that have got tons and tons
of reviews
and feedback, because then you know that their profiles do quite well. And so
it's good to get
inspiration from other people. So then we're thinking about when you've
actually got a call.
So you've answered a call, whether it's a group or a private call doesn't
matter.
First thing we want to think about is what they can actually see and hear. So
this is, as we all
know, there are calls that we call "peepers" that are people that are just
clicking through rooms to
see different people, and they're going to stay for a few seconds and then they
're going to click
off. That's inevitable. We all have them. It doesn't matter if you've been
coming for two weeks or
10 years, we all have those peepers. So this is not about grabbing onto every
single call,
because we can't do that. But there are some people who are flicking through to
see if there's
something inviting, and all of these things here are going to potentially hook
them in to your room
if they're flicking through. So thinking about your screen layouts, I know we
talk about this a lot,
like generally you want to be taking up a good portion of the screen, kind of
like I am right now,
or you might like to have to be a bit further back and have it over there. Some
people use like
a keyboard so that they can see more of your body so that you can kind of show
more of your body
while you're typing while you're talking to them. But generally you want them
to be able to see you
quite well. Of course it's always best to have a HD camera, whether that's on
your laptop or phone
or whatever, if possible. And you can buy some cheap ones, they're not too
expensive on Amazon and stuff.
You want it to be bright and inviting. Obviously we talk about lighting a lot,
so you want to
think about getting a ring light or just, I don't actually have my ring light
on here, and you can
tell because I'm not lit up very well. But usually I'd have my ring light just
behind my laptop,
so that it's really lighting up the screen, and it's really nice to have some
black lights as well,
if you can also get really cheap black lights, less than a tenor on Amazon. I
know that Georgia
likes to have the pink ones in the background, and it just kind of sets the
mood, makes it a bit
more inviting. Obviously you want to think about the setting, so what's in the
background? Are there
things that you have in the background? Are you in bed? Are you one of my
places that does really
well is in my kitchen? I think it's because it's like they're almost feeling
like they're invited
into like a normal space that I'm in, because it's a bit like house-wise vibes,
I think.
I don't normally come here, although it might do quite well. It's like a little
office situation.
But thinking about like the setting is really important, and switching it up
and seeing what works.
Obviously, you know, we're naming the basics here, but thinking about your
posture and whether
you're inviting to them. So, you know, having a nice smile, having an open
posture, you know,
thinking about how you're looking. I mean, the majority of the time, I'm kind
of looking at
myself. I'm not actually looking at the piss, but I'm talking to it. It's
always good to just be
checking in on how you're looking and how inviting you are, isn't it? Of course
, what you're wearing,
you know, kind of goes without saying as well, that goes with the whole vibe
that you're giving.
So, you're thinking, you know, dressing intentionally for cam, whatever that is
, whether it's like,
you know, I love to do gym gear, like these little bras, this like casual core.
But whatever you're
doing, just that it's intentional, and you know that you're bringing a certain
vibe to cam, which
also helps with your confidence as well, doesn't it? If you know you think
comfortable. And I'm also
thinking about the sounds. So, you know, a lot of people will like to have your
audio on.
And that can make your calls last longer with some people. It's totally fine if
you're not able
to do it with the environment that you're in. But if you are able to, even if
you're not talking to
them, it can really help just to have your audio on. If you type to them and
tell them that someone's
in the next room, or for some reason you can't talk, but even just hearing a g
iggle, hearing a laugh,
like hearing a sigh every now and again can really help to engage people and
just give them that extra
element. Okay. So then you've got the client in the room. And we've thought
about like what they can
see. So the immediate, you know, first impression of you. So then we're
thinking about like the
initial connection. So we want to try and engage them quite quickly. So one tip
that we give is just
to greet them like you remember them, even if you don't, which is I'm really
bad at remembering
people. I try and like have a little note down the ones that I think are
important and that I'm
going to need to remember, but it's not always possible, is it? But just
greeting them like you
remember them like you're happy to see them. Hey, it's nice to see you. How's
your day going?
You might like to have a story or opening line or just something you can say
that's kind of
inviting to them and just fun. And we talk about this a lot, but you know, it's
really nice just
to have a few things that you can fall back on, almost become second nature to
you. Like, I bought
this outfit today, because I'm going on a date like I thought I'd try on here.
How's it look? Or
this funny thing happened to me today, you know, or somebody came into my
workplace and they were
really hot, just like a silly, a little opener that you can kind of hook them
in to be interested in
what you've got to say and show a little bit of your personality. So yeah,
having a little opening
story can be a nice like way to get ready for calm as well, just thinking about
like, have you
watched anything that can give you inspiration for a little story or a little,
you know, if it's a
bit flirty and a bit cute or whatever your persona is, then yeah, drawing
inspiration from other things.
As we said, like a genuine smile and positioning your body, it looks good. And
avoiding jumping
straight into performance. I mean, I think this is hard, isn't it? Because it
is acting, you know,
acting is a big part of coming. But we really want to think about presence. We
really want
to think about being present with the person and rather than jumping straight
into what you think
they might want, just taking a few moments to actually, you know, just pause
and really deeply
listen to them. And so, you know, rather than just spewing out something that
you're not sure how
it's going to land, just really taking that time to figure out who this client
is and what it is
they might want to get from this calm session. And in order to do that, you
know, rather than just
going into a performance straightaway, you can just notice how they enter the
space. Just notice,
like, what are they saying? Are they really quick? Or are they a bit slower?
Like trying to mirror
the way that they're showing up. As we've said, some people will leave in
seconds and some people
will take a bit more time, but just trying to get a feel for what they want
when they come into your
room, whether that's attention, relaxation, excitement, whatever it is. So, a
few other tips.
And we were chatting about this, actually, the mentors, we were myself and
Georgia and the
mentors were chatting about that this last week in the run-up to this call and
just thinking about
what it is, some of our top tips, I guess, and the things that we think are
most important when
it comes to engaging your clients and getting them to stay for longer. So,
questions is the first one,
like, yeah, questions, questions, questions. This is the first thing that
pretty much all of us said,
that questions are so important when it's when you're trying to engage with
somebody.
So, just really being curious about what it is they like, you know, if they're
bringing up a
certain topic, it's like, okay, how did you get into that? Or, you know, have
you done this before?
Or, you know, are you here a lot? Or is this a new thing? Like, really honing
in on them and asking
questions. We all know that, you know, most people love to be asked questions
and love to tell you
about what they're thinking, what they're feeling, what they're wanting. So,
just asking as many
open questions as you can so that they can respond and, like, bring themselves
into the space a bit
more fully. Back up stories. So, we did a call a while back about fantasy
writing. And, you know,
what I was saying before about having taking inspiration from something you've
watched or read
or seen and bringing that into camera, like, oh, this thing happens to me today
. It's really good
to have backup stories that you can tell. I mean, one really obvious one, I'm
sure we've all done,
is talking through, you know, what would happen if we were to meet. So, this is
like just an
app classic that most people use with their clients, you know, like, what would
it be like
if you and I met? And sometimes it's like you're saying to the client, you're
saying, oh, you know,
it's a fantasy. So, you know, they might, you might be talking it as if it's
going to happen,
but the majority of the time, we know it's not going to happen. It's just a
fantasy. And so,
don't feel like you're going to have to follow through on whatever you're
saying. But having a
really good and just feeling out, maybe even writing some notes to yourself
when you're not on camera,
when you're waiting for calls, about what it might be like to meet someone, on
how you can draw out
that conversation for as long as possible. So, I like to talk about how I'm
going to feel
when I'm getting ready for them. And, you know, asking them, like, what is it
that you'd like me
to wear? Or, you know, what are you into? And then, where is it? Where are you
going to meet them?
Like, what's that going to be like when you first see them? And then, you know,
how would the flirting
go? You know, would it be a date scenario? How would the flirting go? Would
other people know
what's going on? You know, just explaining in detail. And once you, like, build
up this story
and get used to telling it, you can just add more and more bits when you get
inspiration from
other people about what they like. So, having backup stories that you tell, and
that, like,
classic, how would it be if we met one is just such an easy one to kind of
build on over the
years and really get to know and get your own version of it. And I like to, you
know, I had this
sort of thing where I'm like, you know, I have a fantasy about being paid. So,
I'll tell them all
about this fantasy and about how I'm getting ready for the date and about how
we're flirting
and how I'm feeling, what I'm wearing, and then maybe I'll, like, lift my skirt
up a bit so they
can see. And then I'll be like, well, you know, at some point during the
evening, you'll, like,
offer your slide and envelope across and I'll be, and I'll think about whether
or not I'm going to
take it to the next step, you know, just really, really going in detail at the
same time, like,
using your body and your body language to show that you're kind of into it. So,
you can really,
really work on stories and it can be such an amazing way to engage people and
to get them
coming back again and again. Um, use doing games and using props. So, of course
, we did the love
events call recently and, um, you know, you can use toys and things like that
as props there are
amazing props. Um, but you can also use, like, things that are a little more
out there. I'm thinking
of actually, so I think Sophie's just joined Sophie. What didn't you have? Was
it you that had, like,
a spin, a spinning wheel? Like, what are they called? Those things where you
spin the wheel and
it lands on something. Somebody had one of those. I don't know if it's you,
Sophie. Somebody had
one of those at one point and I thought, Oh my God, that is so fun. That's such
a good idea.
Uh, was it you? Yeah, that was me. Yeah. Yeah. They could set me a couple of
credits and they'd
get to spin the wheel and some of them were like, let's point myself once, you
know,
or flash a booth or a spare or something or it'll be like spin again or it'll
be like,
tip one more credit or, you know, so it was quite good. Um, and the dice game
as well and I'll go.
You've got six numbers on a dice and say the negative numbers
are a punishment. So, like, one, three and five, but like, spank yourself five
times and,
you know, store for whatever and then like two, four and six, like you get, you
know,
two, four and six strokes of your car or whatever they were like, I think.
Yeah. So, like, punishment is a pleasure. It was actually a friend that told me
about that one
and now I use it a lot. Yeah. That's such a good idea. So even just something
you said was a dice.
Yeah. Go on, say. Yeah. If there was a card game, well, it was a board game
with cards on
and you're supposed to play it with a partner and whatever board it was good to
play with on
cam, they could tip credit and ask the question or they tipped you to ask me a
question.
Yeah. It was quite engaging. Yeah, you can even get those level like,
like kinky little question cards and stuff, can't you? Or like the little and
summers type,
you know, little games that you can play on cam.
Yeah. Things you could do with a partner, you can easily adapt it and do it on
cam with
just have a look on love honey website and and some, doesn't it? Well, yeah.
And even she now,
she can do stuff like that now as well, don't they? If you're like on a budget.
Yeah. I got a huge 12 inch devil though from she for like nine pounds.
Yeah, I got a card card card card ring the other day and I was like, yeah, that
was so good.
Yeah. That big toy. It was amazing. I was impressed. Yeah, we definitely keep
clients engaged.
And the other one as well. Yeah. Yeah. So there's loads of ways that you can
use games, you know,
loads of games that you can play with clients that are up for playing them.
And those sorts of things as well. Like, and, you know, don't just need to be
in a private
chart, do they? They can be in a group chart, you know, if you're spinning a
wheel or throwing
a dice or doing something fun like that, you know, you could even do that sort
of thing in free chart,
you know, not without really doing, you know, giving much away, but just as a
way to engage
people and get them in. Yeah, you can feel tip and free. You can still play a
little tip game.
Yeah. Yeah. But a really good way to potentially make some calls last longer,
playing games and using props. And please, like, give us your ideas as well,
girls. If anyone
has any ideas about that, put them in the WhatsApp and love to hear them.
Because I do hear some
unique ways that people are doing games and things. I think it's great. And
using your unique skill.
So, of course, like, you know, many of our girls started working in the clubs
and then
came on to come as they left the club. So obviously, like dancing, things like
that,
what your unique skills are. I mean, they don't have to be just like dancing.
They can be other
things too. But lots of people connect with their clients just by using their
unique skills.
And I really liked this point about Chloe, and if you're there and able to talk
. But the point
that you said about turning no into connection. Yeah. That was me. Yeah,
because I'm the queen.
I've just challenged it, like, basically, basically what it is. Because every
single person, if they've
been on our platform for longer than a week, you always get asked. Even though
it says on your profile
that you don't miss, you always get asked for me. I think it's the most common
thing. I don't even
think all of them mean it. I think it is a lot of fantasy. So that's why if you
say no straight away,
it ruins the fantasy side of things. But that doesn't mean you have to say yeah
. And that's
where the questions, the questions, questions, questions comes in as well.
Because it's like,
oh, I've never done that before, but have you. What is it like? Oh, you might
be persuading me.
Like, if we if you come back and we talk more, I'll be open to the idea. But
what was it like for
you? What is it? What is your pay? Like, how was it? It goes back onto the
question. So they all
help each other. But I've had extra like 10 minute conversations with people
just from that,
where they're like, Oh, like, yeah, I met this girl once and it was good. Or
sometimes they even
say, Oh, it was bad. But I think you'll be different. And I'll be like, Oh, why
? Why did you not enjoy
it? Oh, yeah, I wouldn't do that. And then it goes into a really long
conversation. You're never
going to meet them unless you're comfortable, obviously. But I've been on the
site for over three
years. I've never met a single person. And I've still got some of my clients
from the very first
year that I started being like, I've a convinced to yes. So you're not going to
lose them if you
don't meet them or not all of them. Anyway, some of them do stay around. And
but yeah, as it's like,
when I used to just say no, straight away, I did go straight away. It's a dream
deep literally be
gone. But since saying or maybe all I'm open to it or tell me more about it
first, I've definitely
least like 10 minutes long at the end of a call, which always helps. But even
if it's two minutes,
it all helps. But yeah. And I know what you said in our chat the other day,
play way about like going to Azda or whatever. Oh, yeah. Like we've all went to
Azda for milk.
And came out with everything apart from milk, like everything apart from the
thing that you've
went in for. So it's like, if they ask anything, it doesn't even have to be me
to can be absolutely
anything. If they go in wanting anal, for example, I don't do anal on the site,
but nobody on that
site actually knows that because if they come into my room and say, will you do
this? I'm like,
Oh, yeah, if you get me warmed up first, if we do this, and do you want to see
what my mouth
can do first? Do you want to see what I can do this first? And then they either
forget completely
that the ask for anal or the come way before it gets to that. So they went like
that, like going
into Azda for the thing of milk and coming out with everything. But the thing
you went in for,
but they still enjoy this. They still came and you still get a good review from
it.
Yeah, I love that. I love that analogy of just like just showing them
everything else that,
you know, or any other way to engage with them, you know, and yeah, they don't
really realise that
it wasn't really probably the thing that they really, really needed. It was
just to feel a certain
way, or, you know. Yeah, because it's an experience, isn't it? That's what we
're
selling, isn't it? We're selling an experience. So even if they come in asking
for one that I
don't offer it, say yeah, but let me show you this. And if you're confident
enough,
they really, they just stay there. But again, in the beginning, I would just
normally say now,
like, if anyone came in, I was like, choose, do this, choose, do this, like, oh
, no. And then
again, they'd leave because that's not what they want is or not what these
authority wants is.
So again, it just makes the cause last a lot longer.
Yeah, yeah. I learned that in, like, in my first week, you know, people were
asking,
do you meet, do you meet? And I'd be going, oh God, no. And then,
I got on sick, you know, if you say, yeah, and what are we going to do? And
where are we going to go?
And, you know, the guy with even silly little things like, oh, and I'll take
you for a meal and,
and like, will you hold me hands and, you know, will you hold me out and then,
or do you know,
little stupid things just to keep it going? And I've got fellas who come in my
chat,
they're gilly. And it's a different scenario of what we're going to do and
where we're going to
go and where we're going to stay and where we're going to meet. And, you know,
all over the
friggin country. And it's literally just that fantasy of it, isn't it? You know
, and yeah,
I got on to that super quick because you say, oh no, without me, it's in dong
to go on.
Yeah. And sometimes, like, literally, I've had regulars for years who literally
tell them the
same story. I'm not even like, I'm not even expanding it or editing on it was
to, I'm literally
saying the same thing about what it's going to be like when we meet zippers
going to happen.
And then they go, and then they come back and we do the exact same thing, like,
for years.
The only thing that changes is the friggin dates and the month, that's it. You
know,
the last week, hands in February, we'll get together and we'll do this. Yeah,
all right,
yeah, I'll see you there. Yeah, changing about. Yeah, I think it's really good
to learn quite
quickly that it's just about fantasy, isn't it? It's just about fantasy and
allowing people to be
with you in a fantasy. Of course, there are the odd person that is wanting that
, but for the most
part, we're just, we're just, you know, they're coming towards fantasy and that
's totally fine.
Okay. And then I was thinking about, and you know, I'm happy to have an open
chat about this,
for anyone that has ideas, because I love that we can kind of share ideas, is
that, you know,
based on your Pam persona, and it may not just be one thing that you do, it may
be like a range
of things that you do, or you may just be experimenting and not know fully
right now,
but based on what your persona is, and what your type of client is, there are
lots
of different ideas, there are lots of different ways and things that you can
bring into your
sessions and ways that you can connect with your clients to make your calls
last longer.
So for example, if you are dumb, or being a dumb is like part of what you do,
there are so many
like subgenres of that, that you can research and use in your room. So for
example, you might do
small penis humiliation, and you might do jerk off instruction, and you might
do, again,
like games, or, you know, even things like sort of truth or dare, and if you
get it wrong,
you get a punishment. Obviously, we have a whole course on being a dominatrix,
which is really
useful because it gives some really practical tips about things that you can do
, games you can play,
you know, thinking about agreements and, you know, really fleshing out those
conversations,
and they are amazing if it's something that you're interested in, or you think
you could get into,
they can be amazing clients because they tend to last quite a long time, and
they tend to also
talk to a lot before you get into a session, you kind of do a session, and then
they talk to you
afterwards and wind down from it, so those can be quite lucrative clients and
quite loyal as well.
You can also, as a dumb, give your subs, you know, your regulars things to do
in between
sessions that they can then come and report back to you about, and that can
make calls
less longer and also guarantee that they're going to come back to tell you
about it,
so there's loads of ways that you can make your calls less longer as a dumb.
On the other hand, if you're submissive and you can lean that way and enjoy
doing that kind of thing,
again, you know, there's loads of ways that you can make your calls less longer
.
You can use kind of props. One thing that I used to find quite good is like
using like, well, if you're comfortable, you can do like the candle wax thing,
or even just like
a feather, or a little, a little, you know, a little something to spank or
something,
and get the clients who kind of counts backwards from 10 or something while you
do like little
spanks or little tickles or whatever you're doing on your body so that they can
control
when you're doing it and kind of see your reaction, and those kind of long draw
out things really
make calls last a long time. Obviously, there are some people that just want to
don't really know what domination is, and they're just coming to get an ego
boost,
and they just want to tell you to do this, do that, and that's it, and they're
not actually
willing to spend any money. So just knowing you to invest time and energy into
is a good idea,
but there's also a submissive course in the members area, so loads of ideas as
well,
on how to expand your calls as a submissive. Fantasy we've talked a little bit
about,
this is like something that I've always really been into, just expanding on
people's fantasies.
Again, it's like about questions and really getting to understand maybe what
their kinks are,
or what is they fantasise about, who is involved in those fantasies, like how
can you expand on them
and ask questions about them, and just time on them, because for a lot of
people, they don't
have another outlet or another place to bring their fantasies. So coming to a
space with somebody
who feels genuinely interested or even genuinely turned on about what you're
saying and really wants
to know, can just help you build an amazing relationship with clients. And I've
had some
amazing ones for that reason. I've been so grateful that they've got a space to
come and just explore
how they might expand their fantasy with some ideas that you might bring. So
they could be great
clients. Corny housewife, again, that's another sort of genre and another sort
of persona that
you can try on and embody if you want to. You can sort of ham it up with
details about your
husband who's either like, maybe he's really satisfying you, maybe he's not
like having stories
about that and things that you can say, maybe sort of just bringing your client
in and telling
them in what they think are intimate details or secrets about your relationship
to make them
feel special. Just telling them about how your husband doesn't satisfy you and
that's why you're
here and it's kind of a secret. Any ways that they can feel like they're sort
of in on something
with the horny housewife is a really good way to expand those sessions.
Girlfriend experience, Harry, would you say the girlfriend experience is kind
of what you what you
do most of the time? Would you say that's your thing? Did you say me? Yeah,
yeah, I'd say so or a
lot of it's weird because I actually can't do everything. Like I'm quite open
because because
I ask questions if I don't understand something I just say can you explain it
and then I'll give
it with this girl. So I actually do basically do all of them but I'd say most
of my big
spenders and the clients that come back all the time are like girlfriend's
experience yet. They
want someone sat like this, like I come a lot like this, I dress down, I sit on
the couch, I have
cozy light and not like big bright lights where you can see everything and that
's like I do all
of it but most of the time I do actually just sit and free and stuff like this
and I'm just like,
hi, like and I think it's because it's a very relaxed look. It's like oh kind
of like talking
to your girlfriends on the couch like asking how your day is, like how I can
make it better,
what can I do for you or if I was there I'd do that because a lot of them have
girlfriends
already as well but they want a different one, an online one but yeah it's that
's probably and
they do come back as they but that's when you've got to remember things. I have
a book like a thing
where I've wrote their username and I've wrote things we spoke about because
you will lose them if you forget like you've got to be like oh on Tuesday told
me you were going to
watch a film, what film, what film was it again was it good because the seconds
you start forgetting
things like that they do get really offended because I've lost a lot like that
as well.
And so that's why I have a book now that I can write everything down so I do
remember and it's
it's crazy because it happens to be talking to someone for years and the
seconds I say
oh how was how was your test that you're at on Tuesday when I haven't spoken to
them in a while
that's straight away that like you remember I can't believe you remember that
like
this is why I keep coming back to you because you're so amazing you're so sweet
you really
cared about me too don't yeah and I'm like yeah so like a good girlfriend was
but yeah so I'd
say most of the time it's girlfriend's experience but you can try all of them I
'm actually a dom as
well like it's really funny because sometimes and my sub-men will join a group
that like my
girlfriend's experience person's got me in and I've got to do both so I'm like
yeah like how how
was the cinema on Tuesday and then I'm like oh the other side of it it's like
don't come
yes keep edging like keep going put the cock cage on and then it's like when
worlds collide
and you're like oh god exactly what should I be funny enough these still like
stay there
they still just ignore the other person and then it's double the money but yeah
I do so just but
if you just try one thing you can actually branch out and if someone does come
in your room and says
like do you offer this and you don't know what it is ask I didn't know what J.O
.I. Was until I asked
someone it's like oh J.O.K. Off Instagram I'm like oh okay yeah I can do that
so if you don't understand
something or if you don't know just ask as well because most of the time they
will explain it
yeah yeah going back to the questions thing like I think that I think that's
something that
people sometimes when they first aren't can feel a pressure that they should
know that they should
know things how to do things or what things are called but actually it's
absolutely fine not to
know and it's amazing way to meet your cause that's longer is to ask them is to
get them to teach you
to get them to guide you we all know men love bloody me thinking they know
better than you so
tapping into like the man's playing the baby expert on it you know yeah the all
over man's
playing like sister said yeah cause we're like oh even if I do you know I'm
like oh help me through
it talk me through it and I think I think that's a key thing as well is just
having a girl wasn't
it you know like I am I'm absolutely appalling at being dumb like like
horrendous I put a
wheel off a couch you know what I mean I go oh it's not really my thing but I
will you know let's
have a go and the last one that is is with something that the call was going
really well and
you know I'm telling them things today wouldn't you know like you know you're
not allowed to touch
a cock and did a on all of this and then I told them to go and stand in the
winds out
and and one cause cock to the counter turn in the in this bedroom it called me
ruthless
a longer family was like what but fuck you once you know what I mean that's
just that all of them
I think I've got loads like where I have the conversation like have you got any
limits and
they go I've not got a single limit and I think not a think there's not one
thing you won't do
and then I'm like okay and then I'll say something really basic like I don't
know like go and get
some handcuffs from the room then and the light that's too far and it's like
what you've just
told me that building was what you mean there's no need to be upset to me go
mad
I don't know you're I'm gonna offer me because I'm ruthless and they can't
fucking win
but you know the only thing that matters is that you try is that why you say it
I know
I don't care if I don't care if I don't know what I mean
I've also come back to me week after week and I'm awful at it
I'm still not because I don't think you know they explain to me sometimes what
they want
like they'll send me an email ask would it be an like so for the future session
can you do this
I'm like that's because because I do what I'll learn that's a good point though
because like I think
some people assume that if you're being dumb to someone that you have to make
up everything
that you're gonna do actually a lot of subs they know exactly what they want
they know exactly
how they want it to play out they know what they like to do so it's okay to ask
them like what
does your perfect ham session look like what does what what would a session
look like that you'd
really enjoy what what you not enjoy but you'd like to do like you know just
let them tell you don't
feel like you have to know because everyone's different yeah my stories tell me
what to do more
than I tell them what to do yeah do explain it like they'll say do that I'm
like that mistress
and you're like yeah oh do what you want them okay keep doing that yeah it's
like me like that
is okay topping from the bottom isn't it that that's me in my private life like
I'll tell you I'll
tell you how to don't me I'll tell you what to do yeah I did sometimes these
you just say because
I'll go please don't make me eat my own corn please don't do that that would be
really really
awful mistress and that would be a great punishment if you if you told me to do
it and I'm like okay
and the clues are there aren't you know you're popping your room and the first
thing they say is
hello mistress oh hello goddess yeah yeah yeah right here we go fucking now he
'll be gone in 10
minutes this one right the letter that comes on and is like oh I'm I'm wack
mistress like okay
should we changing happy again then I think I've got the same what changing up
yeah yeah I've got
and it it's got a funny name kw kzw six four or something like that
that's so good nappies is really popular though I had a few like there was I
had this one big
built like he used to walk around like he's holding two tellies covers and
tattoos
and he used to wear a pink frilly nappy on it and I'm waiting it and be like
can you change me
and this is this is crazy yeah please send them my way because I would buzz the
fuck off that
I would have a ball there with grown man in nappy
you can't last though I think that's the first thing you've got to be like
right so when they
show off yeah when they just send the C to C request because they never used to
be able to
do that but so I'm not used to this still because now when the request and I
answered it and it's
something so bizarre I had a man dressed as a pig um not long ago like bent
over oinkin from
the beginning oh I was wrong the beginning and I was like it's that the funky
ones like that
I love that I like that little puggy thing that's why I like the sissies as
well because they're
teddy yeah I love the sissies yeah tell them they put lassen with the sissie I
'm gonna do
the tap sissie then as it would have the grass dresses and sissies because I
need more of that
it's a piece of bits oh and they they are probably my favourite clients they are
just
so nice they aren't this so grateful and so lovely like I just love connecting
with them
and I just have that it's so much fun yeah I love those clients oh you you set
beautiful
where's that from is it yours is it you're wafer yeah it looks amazing popping
up the top of them
knickers yeah blah blah blah blah you know what I mean and they're just sat
there shuffling the
cock away and you don't have to do them yeah they're you think they're putting
a show on for you
some of us man I'm like that's the best thing isn't it somebody putting a show
on for you and
you're just there nice to say to somebody else gives a 12 isn't it yeah yeah
yeah I genuinely like
come on in ladies on the way of how oh yeah no I'm like oh yeah but you're nice
knickers on
yeah to meet a hot one should be fair get your big chest and so it's a bra and
baby
now we need some water you see oh my god
doing a tap straight after this yeah you should do yeah you should do
definitely
because they're because those types of clients were the ones that will look for
that on your profile
as well because yeah you know they want to know that they're safe and they're
okay to do it with
you and so yeah definitely go for that and yeah just the shine innocent is the
last one on there
think the only thing I don't know if anyone's got anything to add on that but I
would just go back
to the questions thing like you know it's all about questions isn't it and just
about you know
allowing yourself to be led and to be taught and you know and to play that role
as well like it's
it's okay to act especially when you first start an outcome maybe you are a bit
shy but
play up to it that's that's okay to do I think I went through them from right
to left in the
last eight years you know two days ago I was shy of this and then I was
girlfriend and horny
only housewife pregnancy breastfeed and all that shit fancy shit bit submissive
and now we're trying
mostly we don't yeah do you know now you've said it that is kind of like the
life cycle of a lot of
power models I think like from right to left yeah yeah yeah that's so true
yeah so a few ideas there um but please like I said there's pretty much
a course or at the very least some calls with ideas about each of these types
of clients and
each of these types of personas that you might have so there's so many ideas on
that the dom course
is really good it's so practical so if you're thinking about it please do that
course because
it's great and then of course uh maintaining contact between cam sessions is
something that
makes your calls last longer so it's not just about what you're doing in the
call it's also about
like building that relationship outside the call as well so giving them
feedback especially after
you've had a good long session with them some you know feedback that shows that
you were listening
and that you enjoyed the call um the new feature which I've not played with and
no
close I think you girls have had a bit of a play with it haven't you like the
instant messaging
thing could be a really good way to keep in contact with clients in between
sessions
um and that's a great new feature I think because we always have said like it's
good to
message or answer your messages maybe while you're waiting for calls or in
between calls or whatever
when you're going on cam you don't want to spend a lot of time and energy on
those because you're
not getting paid for them so this new instant messaging could could be a good I
think that's
what they're doing there they're trying to bridge that gap aren't they and
actually get some money
out of the messaging so um okay it's about the minute you do go on to your
messages and your emails
you will get a call because of the sun's law exactly yeah even if you're just
using it yeah
like you say sun's law um then yes yeah okay so I think that we've come to the
end of the power
point um is there was there a couple of things in the chat I'm wondering if
anyone else has any
questions or tips or anything that they'd like to share
Stella said I'd love any advice on how to set your profile up for GFE
I feel like people just leave if I'm not dressed up
yeah interesting well just because your girlfriend experience does not mean
that you won't be dressed
up and so you might be you might be wearing lingerie or something but you also
might be
just in a little gym kit or pyjamas or something um I think I would say if you
're doing GFE
some people would do their profiles in EFE is some girlfriend experience is
something that I
offer and then talk a bit about that I personally think it's better to kind of
fully live that persona
so just write your profile as if you are that person that you're showing off as
so this is my name maybe even a little bit about your job like I always say
that when I
fist started I used to say I was a nurse because I just thought that was sexy
but it was a good way to just like bring a bit more persona to my profile
because I'd like
say about it maybe have a picture and I'll feel something um so yeah just
writing your
profile as if you are you know just a girl who's showing up here who maybe
wants to chat and connect
with people and this is what I like and this is what I do in my spare time
doesn't have to be like
massively sexual or like professional or whatever actually the more down to
earth it is and the
more believable it is the better most of my profile what you've just said is
right well because most
of my profile I've just had a laugh on it um I've put a little bit like I'm a
switcher I can do
dominance of roles and stuff at the end but all of mine is literally just like
ha ha they covered
up a laugh with me I've just put me own personality on it I've even put on it
don't have to see me
tits because the shit but has to see me boom I've literally got that on there
when that meme was
going around with the hack to girl I put hack to and tip on that thing and then
I put in brackets
me being the thing I like tips like my approach my thing is just funny because
I just thought
you know what I'm having a laugh with it see how far again I've got nothing
about offering
girlfriend's experience or anything but I do get a lot of people who do come in
and be like ha ha
what is your profile and I'm like ha ha and then that's a good conversation
start out there and
because we're both laughing it's not even sexual it then turns in and says oh
you're actually a
really nice girl like I want to get to know you and then sometimes you don't
even have a wank
sometimes you run out of money and even email be being like oh god believe I've
spent all that
money and I didn't even have a wife I had your boss and then they come back so
our minds literally
just like I'll send you or I'll put my profile in the chat and you can read it
if you want it's
literally just a laugh yeah and that but that is like representing your
personality isn't it like
you are fun and so it's a good it's a good representation of you like yeah I
love that I love
that it doesn't have to be serious and it doesn't have to be like professional
or anything just down
to earth and engaging and I think your profile pictures reflect that as well
when my pictures were quite glamorous but then I'm just jumping on in my
kitchen in my pyjamas
I'm not like I felt like people were leaving because it didn't look like that
so I've put really
really casual pictures on mine now and I'm occasionally coming in my glasses
which I used to hate
but now I've put one of my profile pictures of me in glasses dead casual so I'm
quite
girlfriend the experience here without the same as clarry without saying I own
girlfriend experience
it's just like I'm just a normal ish person ish but then bit of dumb bit of sub
bit of it's bit of that
and yeah and it's you know don't try and be something you're not basically the
best
lies I've got a bit of truth and then they make up your persona around what you
do anyway what you
like doing in your personal life just exaggerate it and just love it and just
you're running a bit
have fun with it it is fun job at the end of the day yeah yeah I think that's a
really good point
and you said that didn't you in the week like the best the best lies have a
little bit of truth in
them I think that's so true yeah just like exaggerating or building on stuff
that there's
already a bit of truth in um sorry yeah go on I was thinking about um thinking
about having
two profiles because I get bullied or like a lunatic and it takes me hours to
get ready
and because of the day job that means that well it restricts the times that I
can like just come
on off a weekend and I'd like to be able to jump on for a couple of hours you
know I've been evening
through the week but I cannot be asked with all the rigmarole I go through for
you know putting a
full glam face on and whatever so I also want to have two profiles one that is
more kind of casual
look um because I do also think it's important to kind of your pictures reflect
what they're
gonna say on cam um so well I was thinking about having one kind of you know a
more casual
relaxed look and then the one the one that's running now for like the weekends
when the mall
is up sit similar you know so that the so that being regularism people to do
come and see me know
that it's know that it's still me but probably the same information but the
photos more dressed
down so that I've gone you know for yeah that sounds like so much effort though
but yeah because I
don't care if I accidentally put and make up on they leave if I'm dulled up
they don't care if
I've gotten to make one they don't care I've realised they just don't care the
world I believe
I think I think it's different everyone isn't it because some people it does
really pay for
them to get dulled up I used I used to do that as well I used to be like every
time because I like
what makes hair extensions in proper do the whole thing every time and you are
limited so you can
only have one profile on add at work you can have two you can have two but the
second one has to be
a couple's profile so you would have the option of making a profile with
somebody else if you got
a friend or anyone that is willing to make a profile with you they don't have
to be on there
with you you could just make the profile with them and then be on it yourself
and be like
you know they're out tonight let me second plan is to get above you as well but
yeah okay
yeah so that's the only way that you can make a second profile is to have
someone that does
it with you a lot of girls have like a mate that they see every now and again
and they don't actually
some of them don't come with them very often but it's just a way to have a
second profile really
but I would say is that I think it's okay to I mean you're obviously beautiful
so it's not like you know you need a load of slap on to look attractive you're
gorgeous
and like have coming at different times of the day will you'll have naturally
have different
clients at different so like if you do get glammed I'll put the weekend but
like you're going on a
lunchtime as you are I think that's totally fine like I don't know what you
think if I just like
drops you know you three profile pictures if I had two like glamour glamour
ones and one like
just a home one yeah I think so yeah definitely yeah because some people might
prefer some people
might prefer the more natural lot you know right now yeah I'll stop here don't
point
casual little blankie sat off you know what I mean like oh get in my blanket
with me
yeah yeah yeah yeah because I think when I first started I was like you know
this is my wall paints
and I'm and this is my wallpaper and I'm ready to perform and and I think I've
just made a lot for
me I'm back with it really yeah because like the regulars that are saying the
people to
just you know drop in occasionally and whatever they expect to see me and to be
honest I get a lot
of good feedback on on the big you know glamour pop's look but I can't be asked
for all the time
yeah yeah I think you can just add other strings to your bow like you know like
just as you are now
some little pyjamas or like one thing that because I used to be like that every
single time I get
proper doled up and it took me forever and then I'll be disappointed if I had a
quiet session
on friday friday was appalling for me awful and I'd spent I was getting ready
um and and and it was it was like super shit super shit and maybe in a day
ahead I don't know when
to quit so so I'm sat there for hours you know hours dolls are plating our beds
waiting for
not and instead of going all knocked this on the edge and I'll come back
tomorrow as I go back
the next day and thank god that saturday was a lot better um yeah good but it's
you know when
you just have them shit night sometimes yeah yeah yeah but you just feel like
you wasted just
hand when you've come through all that like my rolled out email and I mean yeah
no I don't think
I think you need to uh what is it say say say say you could take photos and
make videos when you're
all doled off yeah because with the minute I move away from from the computer
the fucking
get on did you do free mode yeah wow did you do free mode I do but it tells me
I said it actually
wouldn't put now it connects with me me lawrence through to the thing it's
definitely um
it's definitely better because I was in in the past it was just doing like
little five minutes
so they went knocking around too long and it drew me as in because sometimes it
well a lot of them
are just sick quiet and I'm sat there thinking you're having a wank for not
nothing not having that
so it was it was it was annoying me but it didn't you know matter how we tried
to engage with them
do you know what I mean trying to talk to them they're just sick quiet so then
I talked to boot
and them you know and it says on me profile because I've got to run down of
what happens in each room
you know private group and and flay um and anosis because I do a lot of profile
switching when it's quiet and see who's got what on and anosis that a lot of
the girls are really
negative on on about it you know if you don't do this if you talk to me like
that if you don't
do that and stuff like that and thought that's really aggressive so mine says
you know it
the ends it on on me free but says you know it's a great way to kind of uh
first introductions
you get to see what I look like and what I'm like and then we can move to a
better room and at the
bottom it says um it's as important that you reply to me messages and reply to
me texting
free because if you just say quiet it makes me feel uncomfortable and that
might lead to you
getting booters out the room basically so that's on there but with with the law
venting there's
something going on you know what I mean and I can go send me a little bose and
you know after time
it's not even in my knickers like hello where did you update and then and and I
just go oh that
was a surprise and you know all of that and and and it gets them really like
engaged with yeah
so so being sorry I'm waffling um being put in like a 20 minute free on now and
that's that the
longer ones and having the law vents has led some more paid gigs really so so
it's not it's not
bearing me as I was as much yeah good yeah good because free can be quite
draining it's not for
everyone definitely not for everyone but I'm glad that's helped and that's kind
of come from one of
the calls that we were chatting about that yeah I still don't understand most
of it because all
these people come for them that I'm dying so that there's one of them wheel
things so thick you can
pick your um pick your hips and and actions and stuff but it was how you get it
on so if anybody
knows please let me know thank you it was so expensive though my axe just
looking got rid of it on me
so we've got there's a couple more questions in the chat let's come to these
before we wrap up
for today so Evie says um do we have any advice on being more of a body
performer I don't show my
face if I talk type and use my body more do you have any advice on that thank
you for any tips
so using your body yeah that's I wonder like what so you do you are talking and
you are typing so
you are still engaging with them in the normal way but you can't not show in
your face and I guess
that that takes away one element doesn't it because it's like you know if when
they can't see your face
or maybe they maybe you're covering your eyes and they can see your mouth maybe
so they can still
see your kind of expression because it's for I guess if they can't see anything
at all that's
quite quite different isn't it hello hello you're here hi good to see you
um yeah so I'm actually doing quite well when I'm feeling on um the whole thing
is working
I'm quite shy I'm blind so um yeah we're just thinking if this maybe I should
dress up a bit sexy
because I haven't just going on like this and I think well if I'm not showing
my face do not get
into this thing but I'm thinking maybe I should dress up a little bit more like
yeah just because I call
it's like yeah yeah definitely like well one thing that I used like to do like
um yeah I think if you
if you've got a mask on then you probably it might be a good idea to dress up a
bit more sexy
because there's more that eyes are drawn to other places rather than to your
eyes um but one thing I
used to like to do is like do massage like massage on my massage myself it's
quite a nice like I
would say like oh I've just got I've got some new oil or something and it looks
so nice on your skin
when it's all shiny under the ring light on cow um so that might be one little
way to like engage
people a bit more I do a lot of body in free when um because I do free all the
time sometimes
me face started and from like smiling everyone coming in so I just do body and
because you've got
a lot of ends as well haven't you? Yeah I think you can do a lot with your body
without showing
your face like even when I giggle if I if you've I've kind of got me belly out
normally but if you
can kind of go like like without showing your face and that's ha ha like if the
same something funny
or waving or like I I do a lot of like but yeah me face so if you can kind of
still see and because
you've got a lovence you can still dramatically be like oh my god I'm coming
without your face
because I do a lot of body especially because um sometimes I'm from the sides I
'll give a like a
little bum wiggle and stuff but you know I wouldn't say you'd have to like
dress up dress up it could
even be like sports bra and shorts like even not even lingerie like you could
even be something
like that or like a silk dressing gown or something that's high and you can
kind of position yourself
to the side like because I do that with free if I want to watch this heli well
like at the same
time so I'm kind of like I'm not even paying it and it does wait I'm half human
then when these
you take me into a room so I've got to be like yeah I like to study I like to
keep moving on anyway
especially when I'm waiting for the reply if five times the wait because
sometimes it can feel a
little bit uncomfortable cutting it and like dada if you if you type in I like
to keep moving
anyway I like to kind of rub rub me fingers and you know like this kind of
thing and play with me
well you know you can play with the bot me red or whatever and just keep your
hands moving on
yourself and a bit a bit of oil and things and if if you don't rub the oil in
like proper proper
you can kind of and your skin's all glistening off and lovely and and then like
blah blah blah
just just keep moving anyway you know what I mean I think I think that's a nice
way to be
visually engaging you know what I mean yeah yeah keep in moving I think that's
really good advice
and I was thinking about layers like having layers or having like things that
you can take
off or slip down or like you know maybe a straps coming down or like having
more layers so there's
a bit more of like a process or even just a pull act it kind of gives the
impression that
you've frustrated you know what I mean yeah pulling it stuff oh you know what I
do actually sometimes
and I don't share my face I've got a coloured and leaves um and I position the
lead sometimes
it looks like they're holding it you know on the thing but you don't have to
get your facing because
it's the colour and then the way the lead is or I sit there like they're
holding it and like playing
with the leads and that that's fantastic because people normally call me
straight away like half
the time people don't even say hi when they see is it with something like so
like out there or
don't see if that's the type of client they're looking for these are all you
straight away and
believe oh my god I love that and you can get a coloured and there's like an
outside one and
like five and on amazon I think that's when it got mad so that's a good idea
because that's not an easy way to play with I think as well because I like
doing that especially
without my face as well because I'm normally like that or telling well I'm in
thing just doing
that waiting for them to say something but that works yeah you know I'm wearing
like jarmy things
and you think the cause that one well you can just like until I button every
now and again and just
pull at your clothes a little bit and make a little or be nice you know a
little
yeah or even like one thing that I you'd quite like in the in the lunch times
like even if I'm
working doing something from home and I'm obviously not dressed up make my sl
obs I just put a shirt
on on top with like a nice roundly so you can like see it through the shirt and
then you've got
something to like slowly unbutton and open shirt I'll go on with the chair open
so you can just see
like cleavage and tittlinging out and it's just like oops and it's like a lot
of on
and I'll do a whole body for that as well I'll just tie my face and just I'll
stand there bored but
all what you're saying you're just touching yourself and rubbing up and down
and to do and
don't let body movements and play in real life be able to record in itself
yeah and and little things like you know pushing you boobs got changing
possession of pushing you
together in things you know boys love you yeah yeah that fun yeah well good to
see you
you be anyway and then yeah let's come to the last question so rose says how do
you get past the
initial interaction the hey like you say hey how are you and they say good you
good what brings you here and then they leave okay yeah um yes I mean as we
said some people won't
won't stay some people won't stay beyond that initial interaction but maybe
like
thinking about some of the things that we've been talking about today so really
thinking about
like how you how you can look how you're lighting is how you're looking because
I'm wondering if
you're feeling a bit stressed about it is that coming across and how you're in
how you're in how
you look you know because you want to be like you know engaging and not not too
worried or anxious
you know and a nice like soft energy so um not putting yourself under too much
pressure that you
have to like that you have to hook every person but maybe like what I was
saying about having a
little thing that you can say rather than just the standard hey how are you
maybe instead of saying
yeah good you you could say something a bit more a bit that has a bit more to
it that's got a bit
more like something that they're going to be able to expand on or interested in
or whatever like yeah
I'm fine like sometimes I'll say like uh I was going to go on a date but they
've cancelled on me
so I'll just come here so I'm not I'm not wasting my outfit or um yeah I've had
I had a long day
in the office but like someone really heart started today so blah blah you know
like just having a
little tidbit I think can just especially if you already know a little thing
that you might say
before the call that helps you to relax because you're like okay yeah I'm gonna
try this thing out
and then it helps them to feel a bit more like you're engaging rather than just
how are you yeah I'm
good because that's I mean let's face it in day to day life that doesn't really
that's not not
very engaging is it like how are you yeah good say that loads of times but it's
it's doesn't I'm
not really thinking about what I'm saying or engaging with the person fully so
sorry I'm gonna
yeah go on go on you think I've been to when there's 40 hundred years the
amounts I've got to
say I you know I love it love it and I think an initial reaction is does
importance as well
if if like once once you hit that accept button if you look genuinely excited
that they're in your
room big smile and like you know even if you're typing like that give them an
impression of genuine
excitement they're like oh oh you know I I think um like I have to remind
myself sometimes when I'm
when I'm tired or I'm or you know just add a shit calling and thinking what the
fuck does this not
bad one now you know what I mean I you pay a bright eyes and kind of you know
big smile and
that idea the genuine excitement kind of gets them on the hook a little better
as well
and and also whatever the I treat it like um does it does the acting technique
in um in in
improvisation uh called yes and so whatever they say whatever their fantasy is
whatever they
whatever their initial conversation is yes and then you add to it and it keeps
things roll and
really nicely so it I think the I prefer to type over talk um because it gives
me that little bit
more thinking time especially if the being a little bit out of my comfort zone
with what what
to say and then stuff and I'm dead slow two finger typing best friends as an
age you know what I mean
um and yes and so yeah was that off topic I don't know no that was totally on
topic I think
that's such a good tip yeah I love that love that yeah just expanding things um
sorry
no because I like I like um like I've got my laptop but I'm like
sitting here and I've got a nice top on and then I've got lacy bra underneath
and I'm like oh
because I get excited every time I get cool because I'm like I don't really get
one very often
so I'm like oh hey how are you and they're like oh good and I'm like oh what
kind of brings like
what brings you here like I'm here to please and then you're like here with the
lacy bra run
and then they just just spin you're like oh okay oh bless you we're gorgeous so
I'm sure
I'm sure they're enjoying looking at you yeah I mean I would say like you don't
even have to say
that yeah I'm good yeah you don't even have to say yeah I'm good you could say
like actually I'm a
bit nervous like I'm quite new to this you know like I'm not really sure how
this goes I'm really
you know like just think you think about what's actually going on for you and
maybe share a bit
more from a from a genuine place you know like I'm just finding my feet um or
anything about being
new then they absolutely lap it up like that's one thing you know having done
this for a long time
that is like annoying because you can't tap into that new market because it's
so good to be just to
be like yeah I'm new I'm a bit nervous not sure how this goes like you know and
that can be a good
opener that can be you know a good way for them to want to engage with you um
what would you try
really would you would you or say if you would you add anything on to that my
um the thing that I say
most of the time is um how can I make your day better or how can I make your
night better if I'm
working in the night very early on because then they tell me exactly what they
want and if they're
nervous or they're new they normally say oh good question what you think or
what can you do or you
know the answer to that right or like it's because I'm asking them a question
or am I what you were
looking for is another one that I say a lot and I always get the same response
of goes answer or
that was a good question this and then it just helps me as well because it's
like okay you're done
oh okay you're so but you want this as well so I do that a lot and I type first
as well I do
afro's you know but nevertheless they ask me because it it takes longer to type
so you can kind of be
like smiling and stuff like that where if you're speaking sometimes even me it
was been doing a
free just I can come across awkward because I'll be like oh god yeah I thought
I'll stuff it all
something I'll be like hot or I'll say something weird and then I'm sat there
bright red thinking
why did I just say that like that like what like I say weird things all the
time
like and I just think oh I should be like I should need to hear my sounds off
so I'm trying to do that for especially with that though because I always
normally get the same
thing it's normally good answer that's why I kept saying it because I was like
okay yeah that's a good
point like it's so much harder I find very very have I very very rarely have I
actually
spoke on cam so much harder to speak because I think it just takes so much more
energy and like
you have to be so quick like typing just gives you a bit more you know it's a
bit more settling and
it gives you a bit more time as you were saying before um maybe it's a good
idea to like just write
down well actually we've got I don't know if you've had it from your mentor but
whoever your mentor
is gonna send it to you we have a list of open questions so you could just have
this like printed
out next to your laptop maybe and just to give you some inspiration in those
moments um but yeah
like if you if you can just think up like two or three little things little tid
bits that you can
say that you could just have there next to you you know I think that's helpful
just like oh yeah
I bought this today or you know this fun thing happens today or you know when
you're saying
how you are just coming with a little bit of something you know to open up a
conversation
there you go Chloe there's a jump for you to do for me yeah I think I think I
might have already
sent you know I think it was in one of the things when we very um when we very
first are so but I'll
send it again or maybe I'll pin it to our chat so you can see it because there
was so much information
in the beginner it is really helpful that it is a lot of it's basically what we
've been saying as
well it is really helpful because it is like how is your day going minds this
or what you do when
they tell or even things like I've just said like am I what what you were
looking for my what you
would expect and like things like that but it is really helpful everything that
's been sent
really helpful to be fair but don't get this heart and see that because also it
could be the
possibility of they were going to do that anyway like it didn't matter what you
says how you look
how you start at the core there is just a lot of people that you just go
straight away sometimes
they don't even let it connect and you don't even get paid for it and then they
don't even try and
call you to call you back as they'll end it straight away and you think you
haven't even seen me um
it does just happen a lot as well so don't get as heartened if even you do try
these new things
if it still happens like it literally it happens to every single one of us
yeah yeah so certain that I do as well that like to type and because I do
purposely take me
time typing to kind of cut that quiet because I have me all do I want um but I
do type and it
and and if they say oh do you talk I do say I do talk in private but it's weird
if I'm typing in
your talk and and they take that as a they take that as a given and they go all
right but I have
like I have like proper sexy music on in the background like and so it takes it
the sort like
this music's on about shag and deep throat and doo doo doo doo doo and I
thought I was
flowy I was like can I have some music on in the background or something and
she was like yeah
yeah I I I I I dropped some some um some tracks in there in the in the social
and if you just
put that put put that into specifying and then let it let it roll through and
and honestly so
god you you'll be craving you next is within half an hour let alone then we'll
have honestly
it's proper proper good gear and it just keeps well I feel like it causes that
kind of
sexy talk music it doesn't really matter how long it takes like because the
songs do and
the sexy talk for you as well do you know what I mean if that makes sense yeah
he likes that
you know it also gives away like awkward silence as well like when you're just
there with you
like he's just silent you just kind of away yeah it's not maybe a boy is it
yeah yeah I have a
little bond I'm also I don't know like if you're like the way you are now is
what you would typically
like your setup is like um rose but okay yeah no I don't mean as in like what
you're wearing
but I'm thinking about the lighting like you've got such a beautiful phase I'm
wondering if you've
got a ring light normally or like a bit more light behind the camera front of
you yeah normally I do
have a bit more light um yeah I've literally just finished my hair that's just
getting ready for
I just thought I'd sit here and show you like whoa this should I was sort of
like yeah I'm on a
laptop as well but it's sort of like this and you're sort of yeah a long top
that sort of comes
down to here and then a little lacy bralette and then you're just like and then
I'm like oh hello
and then they're just like I'm so excited I don't know
no I think it's great and I'm sure you'll find your feet I'm sure you'll find
your feet um so yeah
I'm coming to the cause great things to do today I get some inspo and some
motivation from everyone um okay lady so well it's um just coming up to ten o'
clock soon
just about on time uh to finish like all day but thank you so much thank you to
everyone that came
there's a couple of people that popped in and out throughout um but thank you
to everyone
ask the question rose it was lovely to meet you um lovely to see the rest of
the gang they look
great to see you as well thank you so much for the tips that you gave you've
been great um and yeah
we're gonna have another it's gonna be a mental health check-in at the end of
the month um
so I'll post about that tomorrow I was just gonna wait till after this call to
post about that
and then don't forget for anyone that is wanting to come we're doing a photo
shoot in december
uh I want to say like the fifth something like that it's a saturday the first s
aturday in december
in london so if anyone wants to come to that that's open to everyone um and we
're also going for
a night out afterwards so please even if you just want to come for the night
out and party with us
um it's um oh I can't wait to see you two thank you for coming um yeah we're
gonna be going to be
hemian spirits which is a party from a friend of a friend of mine's party it's
amazing it's like
it's dress up the theme is vikings so we're gonna be doing some viking dress up
after the shoot it's
just a lot of fun the music's amazing the crowd's amazing it's really like sex
positive queer
lovely crowd um all my lovely friends um so yeah you're more than welcome to
come to the shoot
message a mentor or me and I can give you the details or just come for the
night out if you want
to um so yeah can you repost about the above the night out bit where to get the
tickets from please
out because we're going to try me very best to sort it out okay yeah that would
be great yeah
yeah come on party with us it's gonna be so much fun and we've got Georgia is
back from australia
tailand she's always somewhere other she's back for she only comes back once a
year and she's back so
I'm so excited that we'll talk together um yeah so it'd be really fun yeah I'll
post about it again
in the group um yeah so thank you everybody so good to see you thank you to the
mentors as well
thank you very much you all nanae guys mwah see you all soon